<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-06-23T10:47:12+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Center for Human-Engaged Computing</title><subtitle>Center for Human-Engaged Computing,  Kochi University of Technology， Tosayamada, Kami City，Kochi,  JAPAN P:+81-887-57-2087 © 2019-2020 All Rights Reserved.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">The 34th CHEC/82th Renlab Workshop</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2022/02/08/The-35th-CHEC-83th-Renlab-Online-Workshop.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The 34th CHEC/82th Renlab Workshop" /><published>2022-02-08T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2022-02-08T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2022/02/08/The-35th-CHEC---83th-Renlab-Online-Workshop</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2022/02/08/The-35th-CHEC-83th-Renlab-Online-Workshop.html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/52408689088_b1b0a6a1fe_c.jpg" alt="Figure" /></p>

<p>Keynote: Prof. Ruck Thawonmas and doctoral candidate Pujana Paliyawan</p>

<p>Abstract:　Due to the new crown virus, this lecture will be held online. In this lecture, our workshop use sessions to divide 2 different talks.</p>

<p>Session I Chair: Tan	
 10:05 - 10:45	Zhihang GUO	‘How to understand Dynamic Difficulty Adjustment: A New Definition’，	
 10:45 - 11:00	Koyama	‘A more time-efficient HIIT mechanism for self-control training’，	
 11:00 - 11:20	Yibin JIA	‘Emotion-based Dynamic Difficulty Adjustment’，	
 11:20 - 11:40	Takaaki Kubo	‘PX at different of Difficulty Adjustment Methods in a cognitive motion VR game’，	
 11:40 - 11:55	Koki Uchida	’Zoo Feeder Game Introduction‘，
 11:55 - 12:20	Junlin SUN	‘A Novel Difficulty Mechanism based on HIIT for Self-control Training Game Design’.</p>

<p>Session II Chair: Guo	
 14:00 - 14:40	Chen WANG	‘Towards Human-Engaged Computing: Design Guidelines and Interface Aesthetics ’.</p>

<p>Session III Chair: Wang	
 14:50 - 15:30	Peng TAN	‘Understanding Rhythm in HCI’,	
 15:30 - 15:55	Xiaofei ZHU 	‘A Soundscape Interaction System for Enhancing Mindfulness While Running’,	
 15:30 - 15:45	Ryo Kumamoto	‘Support for running meditation using I’m thinking of doing’,	
 15:45 - 16:00	Mahiro Tsuda ‘Walking/running creativity by interactive soundscapes’,	
 16:00 - 16:15	Wakasa Noguchi	‘Hi-Low Tech Ombro-Cinema’,	
 16:15 - 16:30	Hidetaka Okumura	 ‘Hybrid Moving Image’,	
 17:00 - 17:30	Keynote Speaker: Kavous Salehzadeh Niksirat	‘Addressing Multiparty Privacy Conflicts in Online Social Networks’,	
 17:30 - 17:35	Prof. Hoshino give the closing speech.</p>]]></content><author><name>Yibin JIA</name></author><category term="Events," /><category term="Talks," /><category term="Visitors" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">International Workshop on Human-Engaged Computing 2021</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2021/03/21/International-Workshop-on-Human-Engaged-Computing-2021.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="International Workshop on Human-Engaged Computing 2021" /><published>2021-03-21T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2021-03-21T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2021/03/21/International-Workshop-on-Human-Engaged-Computing-2021</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2021/03/21/International-Workshop-on-Human-Engaged-Computing-2021.html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/51100665473_f76e0cde8c_z.jpg" alt="Figure" /></p>

<p>The Center for Human-Engaged Computing (CHEC) will organize an international workshop on Human-Engaged Computing (IWHEC 2021). The workshop will be convened online via ZOOM and it will be open to all audiences around the world through webcasts and/or live-streaming platforms.</p>

<p>The aim of this workshop is to rethink the relationship between humans and computers. The workshop will strive to achieve a common platform to advance various idea exchanges around the world, resulting in the evolution of a stronger workforce in order to create a better world to live in. We are inviting distinguished speakers from around the world and from several domains such as human-computer interaction, brain science, computer science, AI, engaged human, engaging technology, design so on.</p>

<p>HP: http://iw2021.xrenlab.com/</p>

<p>Invited Speakers:</p>

<p>1)	Jonathan Grudin, Microsoft Research, United States
Title: Engaging with a Virtual Companion</p>

<p>2)	Gilbert Cockton, University of Sunderland, United States<br />
Title: Engaging Humanities with Worthwhile Computing</p>

<p>3)	Prof. Hong Z. Tan, Purdue University, United States<br />
Title: The Science and Art of Conveying Information through Touch for Human-Engaged Computing</p>

<p>4)	Prof. Gloria Mark, University of California, Irvine <br />
Title: 47 Seconds of Focus: Distractions, Stress and Productivity in our Digital Experience</p>

<p>5)	Prof. Anirudha Joshi, IDC School of Design, IIT Bombay, India
Title: Designing for and with Emergent Users</p>

<p>1)  Miwako Doi, NICT(National Institute of Information and Communications Technology), Japan<br />
Title: Interaction with Data-driven Society</p>

<p>7)	Kazuhisa Shibata, RIKEN Center for Brain Science, Japan
Title: Perceptual and Cognitive Changes Induced by Decoded Neurofeedback</p>

<p>8)	Abhishek Gupta, Montreal AI Ethics Institute, Canada 
Title: Designing for Humans: Getting Responsible AI in Practice</p>

<p>9)	Prof. Fang You, Tongji University, China<br />
Title: Design Guidelines for the Size and Length of Chinese Characters Displayed in the Intelligent Vehicle’s Central Console Interface</p>

<p>10)	Jian Zhao, University of Waterloo, Canada
Title:  Support Effective Decision Making by Engaging Humans with Predictive Models via Interactive Visualization</p>

<p>11)	Johanna Schmidt, VRVis Research-GmbH, Austria
Title:  Data visualization literacy as a key for data understanding</p>

<p>12)	Prof. Ying-Qing Xu, Tsinghua University, China
Title:  Social Responsibility of Design Innovation</p>

<p>For more details, please click http://iw2020.xrenlab.com/</p>]]></content><author><name>Lancy LAN</name></author><category term="Events," /><category term="Talks," /><category term="Visitors" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The 33th CHEC/81th Renlab Workshop</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/11/03/The-33th-CHEC-81th-Renlab-Online-Workshop.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The 33th CHEC/81th Renlab Workshop" /><published>2020-11-03T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2020-11-03T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/11/03/The-33th-CHEC---81th-Renlab-Online-Workshop</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/11/03/The-33th-CHEC-81th-Renlab-Online-Workshop.html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/50594013966_0fb516a3d9_c.jpg" alt="Figure" /></p>

<p>Keynote: Zhiwei Luo</p>

<p>Prof. Zhiwei Luo Bio: Zhiwei Luo received his M.E. degree and Ph.D degree from Nagoya University, Japan, in 1991 and 1992, respectively. 
He was an assistant professor in Toyohashi University of Technology in 1992, a frontier researcher of RIKEN in 1994 and associate professor of Yamagata University in 1999. He was a team leader of RIKEN in 2001, where he leaded the development of the world first human care robot RI-MAN. Since 2006, he is a professor in Kobe University. 
His research interests include System Control, Robotics, Human Computer Interface, and Health Engineering. 
He honored Fellow of SICE in 2016 and is currently a board member of SCI, Japan</p>

<p>Abstract:　Due to the new crown virus, this lecture will be held online. In this lecture, our workshop use sessions to divide 3 different talks.</p>

<p>Session Keynote and Game for Cognition Enhancement 1, Chair: Junlin Sun:   	<br />
 10:00 - 10:05 Prof.Ren give us a opening speech, 	
 10:05 - 10:45 Prof. Zhiwei Luo talk about ‘Innovation of Health Robotics for Aging Society’, 	
 10:45 - 11:20 Xinhui Jiang ‘Understanding the Relationship between Eye Properties and Flow Experience in Game’, 	
 11:20 - 11:35 Jian Zhang and Saki Hiramatsu ‘Adaption of eye and finger behavior on new keyboard layouts’,	 
 11:35 - 11:50 Zhihang Guo ‘How cognitive exergame difficulty influence the effect of cognitive enhancement of the elderly’, 	
 11:50 - 12:05 Hongyun Lyu ‘How game control device impact player engagement’, 	
 12:05 - 12:20 Sai Jiang ‘Research on the Design of writing Expression App to adjust the anxiety of postgraduate students’.</p>

<p>Session Game for Cognition Enhancement 2 and HEC: 		  	
13:20 - 13:40 Li Yang ‘Designing Successive Target Selection in Virtual Reality via Pene-trating the Intangible Interface with Handheld Controllers’,	 
13:40 - 13:55 Yilin Zheng ‘Exploring Text Revision with Backspace and Caret in Virtual Reality’, 	
13:55 - 14:10 Xiaofei Zhu ‘Exploring the mindfulness running experience with soundscape interaction application’, 	
14:10 - 14:25 Junlin Sun ‘The design of self-control training game with super compensation theory’, 	
14:25 - 14:40 Lancy (Chunyuan Lan) ‘Binaural effect in Meditation’.</p>

<p>Session Conventional HCI Group: 	 	
14:50 - 15:10 Xinpeng Li(Akinori Kondo+Yusuke Tokito) ‘Comparing the Aesthetic Perception on Webpage Metrics between Chinese and Japanese Users’,	 
15:10 - 15:25 Xi Chen ‘The influence of fuzzy interaction design on improving the online audience’s focus’, 	
15:25 - 15:40 Takaki Kubo Hiramatsu ‘FarmAnimal: A VR Motion Video Game for Older Adults to Prevent Cognitive Decline’, 	
15:40 - 15:45 Adachi Kenshi ‘New reporting system in the lab’, 		 
15:45 - 15:50 Xiangshi Ren Closing Speech.</p>]]></content><author><name>Lancy LAN</name></author><category term="Events," /><category term="Talks," /><category term="Visitors" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The 32th CHEC/80th Renlab Workshop</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/07/19/The-32th-CHEC-80th-Renlab-Online-Workshop.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The 32th CHEC/80th Renlab Workshop" /><published>2020-07-19T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2020-07-19T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/07/19/The-32th-CHEC---80th-Renlab-Online-Workshop</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/07/19/The-32th-CHEC-80th-Renlab-Online-Workshop.html"><![CDATA[<p>Keynote: Yoshiko Yabe</p>

<p>Dr. Yoshiko Yabe Bio: Dr.Yoshiko Yabe is currently a Research Specialist at NTT Communication Science Laboratories, Nippon Telegraph and Telephone Corporation, Japan since 2018. She was an Assistant Professor at Kochi University of Technology from 2011 to 2013. She was a postdoc fellow at the Brain and Mind Institute, the University of Western Ontario in Canada (Melvyn Goodale Lab.) from 2013 to 2018. She has worked on projects in psychology and neuroscience about how physical actions affect perception. She started focusing on time perception during her first postdoc at KUT and now working on a project to improve sport performance using the effect of action on time perception.</p>

<p>Abstract:　Due to the new crown virus, this lecture will be held online. In this lecture, our workshop use sessions to divide 4 different talks.</p>

<p>Session Keynote and Game for Cognition Enhancement 1: 	
 10:00 - 10:05 Prof.Ren give us a opening speech, 	
 10:05 - 10:45 Dr. Yoshiko Yabe talk about ‘Time flies forward/backward when you intend to act’, 	
 10:45 - 11:20 Eloise (Xiaoxuan Li) and Takaaki Kubo Review of  motion video game about cognitive enhancement, 	
 11:20 - 11:35 Zhihang Guo and Miyamoto Daisuke The relation between human and game under the HEC perspective, 	
 11:35 - 11:50 Hongyun Lyu The impact of game input devices on user engagement.</p>

<p>Session Game for Cognition Enhancement 2 and HEC:  	
12:50 - 13:10 Li Yang Facilitating Text Input in Mobile and Virtual Reality Interfaces, 	
13:10 - 13:25 Yilin Zheng Text Revision in VR, 	
13:25 - 13:40 Sai Jiang The influence of persuasive design on diary writing 	
13:40 - 13:55 Lancy (Chunyuan Lan) Binaural effect in Meditation.</p>

<p>Session Conventional HCI Group: 	
14:05 - 14:25 Xinhui Jiang A Study of Eye and Finger Behaviors for Text Input on Mobile Devices, 	
14:25 - 14:40 Zhang Jian Investigation on the Strategies of Fast Typist on Mobile Devices , 	
14:40 - 14:45 Saki Hiramatsu Understanding Learning and User Behavior Adaption on Randomized Keyboards, 	
14:45 - 15:00 Fitra Rahmamuliani Effective Planning and Reporting in Academic Research Labs - Challenges and Opportunities, 	
15:00 - 15:05 Adachi Kenshi Current Activities and Future Outlook.</p>

<p>Session Aesthetics and Reporting System: 	
15:15 - 15:45  Chen Wang (Xinpeng Li, Yusuke Tokito, Akinori Kondo) Visual Homogeneity: A Computational Metric for GUI Aesthetics Design / Comparing the Aesthetic Perception on Webpage Metrics between Chinese and Japanese Users, 	
15:45 - 16:00 Junlin Sun A new paradigm for designing self-control training game, 	
16:00 - 16:15 Xi Chen Focus in tele-cooperation, 	
16:15 - 16:30 Xiaofei Zhu Explore the mindfulness running experience using soundscape interaction application, 	
16:30 - 16:35  Xiangshi Ren Closing Speech.</p>]]></content><author><name>Lancy LAN</name></author><category term="Events," /><category term="Talks," /><category term="Visitors" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keynote: Yoshiko Yabe]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The 31th CHEC/79th Renlab Workshop</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/04/11/The-31th-CHEC-79th-Renlab-Online-Workshop.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The 31th CHEC/79th Renlab Workshop" /><published>2020-04-11T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2020-04-11T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/04/11/The-31th-CHEC---79th-Renlab-Online-Workshop</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/04/11/The-31th-CHEC-79th-Renlab-Online-Workshop.html"><![CDATA[<p>Abstract:　Due to the new crown virus, this lecture will be held online. In this lecture, our workshop use sessions to divide 3 different talks.</p>

<p>First Session :  	
 13:00 - 13:05 Prof.Ren give us a opening speech, 	
 13:05 - 13:25  Hamed Aliyari Brief reseach plan in the following 3 years -VIDEO, 	
 13:25 - 14:05 Xinhui Jiang(Jian Zhang) Understanding the Fast Typists on Mobile Devices,  	
 14:05 - 14:20 Junlin Sun  Game design intended for the purpose of improving self-control imperceptibly, 	
 14:20 - 14:35 Xiaofei Zhu Research on the behavior characteristics of eye movement analysis for safe driving.</p>

<p>Second Session :  	
14:45 - 14:50 New 3rd yr stu Self Introduction by Adachi Kenshi(足立 剣士), 	
14:50 - 14:55 New 3rd yr stu Self Introduction by Daisuke Miyamoto(宮本 大輔), 	
14:55 - 15:10 Zhihang Guo Game Definition, 	
15:10 - 15:25 Xi Chen Support system for shift workers, 	
15:25 - 15:40 Hongyun Lyv Factors effect text entry performance, 	
15:40-  16:20  Chen Wang
(XinPeng Li/ Yusuke Tokito/ Akinori Kondo) Homogeneity: A Computational Aesthetics Metric in Supporting GUI Design Optimization.</p>

<p>Third Session :  	
16:30 - 17:10  Yang Li (Yilin) Facilitating Text Input Performance in Mobile and Vitrual Applications &amp; Chunyuan Lan Binaural effect in  Meditation, 	
17:10 - 17:25 Eloise(Takaaki Kubo) Design a Motion Video Game to Enhance the Cognitive of the Elderly , 	
17:25 - 17:40 Fitra Rahmamuliani Reporting and Planning in Research Teams; Challenges and Opportunities, 	
17:40 - 17:45  Xiangshi Ren Closing Speech.</p>]]></content><author><name>Lancy LAN</name></author><category term="Events," /><category term="Talks," /><category term="Visitors" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract:　Due to the new crown virus, this lecture will be held online. In this lecture, our workshop use sessions to divide 3 different talks. First Session : 13:00 - 13:05 Prof.Ren give us a opening speech, 13:05 - 13:25 Hamed Aliyari Brief reseach plan in the following 3 years -VIDEO, 13:25 - 14:05 Xinhui Jiang(Jian Zhang) Understanding the Fast Typists on Mobile Devices, 14:05 - 14:20 Junlin Sun Game design intended for the purpose of improving self-control imperceptibly, 14:20 - 14:35 Xiaofei Zhu Research on the behavior characteristics of eye movement analysis for safe driving.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Research Internship Experience in CHEC</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/03/10/A-Research-Internship-Experience-in-CHEC.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Research Internship Experience in CHEC" /><published>2020-03-10T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2020-03-10T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/03/10/A-Research-Internship-Experience-in-CHEC</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/03/10/A-Research-Internship-Experience-in-CHEC.html"><![CDATA[<p>At that time, I was confused because my ability couldn’t keep up with my ambitions and I didn’t know how to improve it. But again, I learned a lot from the CHEC Weekly Sharing Session, including methods of research, ways of thinking and living habits. Gradually, everything became clear and the vital thing I need to do is to take the first step.</p>

<p>I feel super grateful for CHEC members because they taught me how to find the life goal and the ways to achieve it. I finished the internship with two great things CHEC gave to me, and I will move forward with it, step by step.</p>]]></content><author><name>Yanyin Zhou</name></author><category term="Events," /><category term="Talks," /><category term="Visitors" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[At that time, I was confused because my ability couldn’t keep up with my ambitions and I didn’t know how to improve it. But again, I learned a lot from the CHEC Weekly Sharing Session, including methods of research, ways of thinking and living habits. Gradually, everything became clear and the vital thing I need to do is to take the first step.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Prof. Hideaki Kuzuoka from The University of Tokyo visited CHEC</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/01/17/Prof.-Hideaki-Kuzuoka-from-The-University-of-Tokyo-visited-CHEC.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Prof. Hideaki Kuzuoka from The University of Tokyo visited CHEC" /><published>2020-01-17T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2020-01-17T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/01/17/Prof.%20Hideaki-Kuzuoka-from-The-University-of-Tokyo-visited-CHEC</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/01/17/Prof.-Hideaki-Kuzuoka-from-The-University-of-Tokyo-visited-CHEC.html"><![CDATA[<p>Hideaki Kuzuoka is a Full Professor at the Graduate school of Information Science and Technology, The University of Tokyo. His main research field is CSCW/groupware. While he got his bachelor’s degree from Mechanical Engineering and his preference for gadgets, he is one of the pioneers who introduced robots and gadgets to CSCW research. He has been working with Ethnomethodologists for more than 10 years and the research formation enable them the long-term iteration of development and evaluation cycle. The research group is well known  to the CSCW and HCI (Human Computer Interaction) communities in the world and their papers are continuously accepted by the highly rated international conferences like CHI, CSCW, and ECSCW.</p>]]></content><author><name>Lancy LAN</name></author><category term="Events," /><category term="Talks," /><category term="Visitors" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hideaki Kuzuoka is a Full Professor at the Graduate school of Information Science and Technology, The University of Tokyo. His main research field is CSCW/groupware. While he got his bachelor’s degree from Mechanical Engineering and his preference for gadgets, he is one of the pioneers who introduced robots and gadgets to CSCW research. He has been working with Ethnomethodologists for more than 10 years and the research formation enable them the long-term iteration of development and evaluation cycle. The research group is well known to the CSCW and HCI (Human Computer Interaction) communities in the world and their papers are continuously accepted by the highly rated international conferences like CHI, CSCW, and ECSCW.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Prof. Liao Chiyang from Musashino Art University visited CHEC, Kochi University of Technology</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/01/14/Prof.-Liao-Chiyang-from-Musashino-Art-University-visited-CHEC,-Kochi-University-of-Technology.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Prof. Liao Chiyang from Musashino Art University visited CHEC, Kochi University of Technology" /><published>2020-01-14T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2020-01-14T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/01/14/Prof.%20Liao-Chiyang-from-Musashino-Art-University-visited-CHEC,%20Kochi-University-of-Technology</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/01/14/Prof.-Liao-Chiyang-from-Musashino-Art-University-visited-CHEC,-Kochi-University-of-Technology.html"><![CDATA[<p>一指禅功伝承者,日本無為気功養生会代表,世界医学気功学会常務理事・学術委員会委員, 武蔵野美術大学　教授</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Events," /><category term="Talks," /><category term="Visitors" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[一指禅功伝承者,日本無為気功養生会代表,世界医学気功学会常務理事・学術委員会委員, 武蔵野美術大学　教授]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">International Workshop on Human-Engaged Computing 2020</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/01/10/International-Workshop-on-Human-Engaged-Computing-2020.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="International Workshop on Human-Engaged Computing 2020" /><published>2020-01-10T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2020-01-10T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/01/10/International-Workshop-on-Human-Engaged-Computing-2020</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2020/01/10/International-Workshop-on-Human-Engaged-Computing-2020.html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49413253857_6a89b8cc8c_c.jpg" alt="Figure" /></p>

<p>The Center for Human-Engaged Computing (CHEC) will organize an international workshop on Human-Engaged Computing (IWHEC 2020). The workshop will be held at Kochi University of Technology in Japan on January 10th 2020.</p>

<p>The aim of this workshop is to rethink the relationship between humans and computers under consideration of human future. The workshop strives to achieve a common platform to increase various idea exchanges around the world, resulting evolvement of stronger workforce in order to create a better world to live in. In this workshop, we will invite seven experts to give their points of view of HEC practice.</p>

<p>HP: http://iw2020.xrenlab.com/</p>

<p>Keynote Speech:</p>

<p>1)	Prof. Zhiyong Fu, Tsinghua University, China 
Title: Empathy and Symbiosis: Design preferable future AI product and service</p>

<p>2)	Prof. Jeffrey Bardzell, Indiana University, United States 
Title: “Knowledge Embodied in Artifacts”: A Problem in Design Epistemology</p>

<p>3)	Prof. Shaowen Bardzell, Indiana University, United States 
Title: Women’s Health in HCI: A Feminist Utopian Design Approach to Menopause Wellness</p>

<p>4)	Dr. Xiaojuan Ma, Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, China 
Title: Manifesting AI Engagement in Human-Engaged Computing</p>

<p>5)	Dr. Xiaojun Yuan, University at Albany-SUNY, United States
Title: Voice Search and Human-Engaged Computing</p>

<p>6)	Dr. Byungjoo Lee, Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology, Korea 
Title: Understanding Human-Computer Synchronization: From a Human-Engaged Computing Perspective</p>

<p>7)	Prof. Jianmin Wang, Tongji University, China
Title: Make Automated Drive Acting like a Man based on the Collaborative Driving Synergized Interaction</p>

<p>For more details, please click http://iw2020.xrenlab.com/</p>]]></content><author><name>Lancy LAN</name></author><category term="Events," /><category term="Talks," /><category term="Visitors" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Prof.Masaki Nakagawa from Tokyo University of Agriculture and Technology visited CHEC, Kochi University of Technology</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2019/12/20/Prof.Masaki-Nakagawa-from-Tokyo-University-of-Agriculture-and-Technology-visited-CHEC,-Kochi-University-of-Technology.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Prof.Masaki Nakagawa from Tokyo University of Agriculture and Technology visited CHEC, Kochi University of Technology" /><published>2019-12-20T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2019-12-20T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2019/12/20/Prof.Masaki-Nakagawa-from-Tokyo-University-of-Agriculture-and-Technology-visited-CHEC,%20Kochi-University-of-Technology</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/events,/talks,/visitors/2019/12/20/Prof.Masaki-Nakagawa-from-Tokyo-University-of-Agriculture-and-Technology-visited-CHEC,-Kochi-University-of-Technology.html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49268938772_8a1f70473c_z.jpg" alt="Prof.Masaki Nakagawa from Tokyo University of Agriculture and Technology visited CHEC" /></p>

<p>Prof.Masaki Nakagawa from Tokyo University of Agriculture and Technology visited CHEC and gave two talks entitled “Latest Applications of Deep Neural Networks to Handwriting Recogintion and Identification” and “人を育て，地域を潤し，大学を伸ばす知的創造サイクル”.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Events," /><category term="Talks," /><category term="Visitors" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry></feed>